ACTWU's Secretary-Treasurer's Office Records 5619/018
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Atlantic Mills: San Antonio Statements, 1963-1971 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Atlantic Mills: Texas Statements, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Atlantic Mills: Fort Worth Statements, 1963-1969 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Atlantic Mills: Grand Rapids Statements, 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Atlantic Mills: Jacksonville Reports, 1962-1971 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Atlantic Mills: Kansas City Reports, 1963-1969 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Atlantic Mills: Knoxville Reports, 1962-1971 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Atlantic Mills: Lansing Reports, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Atlantic Mills: Memphis Reports, 1962-1971 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Atlantic Mills: Milwaukee Reports, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Atlantic Mills: Cleveland Reports, 1962-1966 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Atlantic Mills: Columbia, SC Reports, 1962-1970 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Atlantic Mills: Corpus Christi Reports, 1963-1969 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Atlantic Mills: Des Moines Reports, 1962-1970 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Atlantic Mills: Dallas Reports, 1963-1967 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Shoppers Fair Contracts, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Arlans Settlements, 1963-1967 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Atlantic-Spartan: Bessemer Reports, 1967-1969 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- AFL-CIO: Retail Cases, 1963-1966 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Atlantic Mill: Alexandria Reports, 1963-1966 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Atlantic Mills: National Correspondence, 1963-1967 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Atlantic Mills: Birmingham Reports, 1962-1968 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Atlantic Mills: Atlanta Reports, 1963-1969 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Atlantic Mills: Charlotte Reports, 1963-1968 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- ATC Contracts, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Spartan-Atlantic: Minneapolis Negotiations, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- ACWA: Joint Board Reports, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Atlantic Mills: Oklahoma City Reports, 1964-1968 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- ACWA: Appeals Committee Report, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Atlantic Mills: Norfolk, VA Report, 1963-1968 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Atlantic Thrift Center New Orleans Report, 1965-1969 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Atlantic Mills: Mobile Reports, 1962-1972 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Atlantic Mills: Minneapolis Report, 1962-1967 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- ACWA Appeals Committee Report, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Layers-Off: Gloversville Report, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- ACWA General Executive Report, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- ACWA Product Statements, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Warren Rash Letters, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Arpie Ruth: Report and Recommendations, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- ACWA: Financial Statements, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- ACWA: Biennial Convention Reports, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- ACWA: Committee on Banking Reports, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- ACWA: General Membership Referendum Charts (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Gloves Cities Dues Reports, 1962-1964 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Glove Industries Negotiations, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- United Glove Workers Merger Notes, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Glove Industry Negotiations, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Philadelphia Appeal Notes, 1963-1972 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- VAL Testimony Notes, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Education Program, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- The Nation's Public Schools Reports, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Union Label Campaign, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Resolution on Organizing, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Walsh-Healey Public Contracts Act, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Workmen's Compensation Resolution, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Unemployment Insurance Resolution, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Taft-Hartley and Landrum-Griffin Laws, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Resolution and Repeal of 14B, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Social Security Act Resolution, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Economic Opportunity Act, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- The Nation's Health, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Fair Labor Standards Act Resolution, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Civil Rights Resolution, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Congressional Reform Statements, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Resolution on Political Education, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Resolution on Day Care Centers, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Consumer Problems Reports, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Boys' Towns and Girls' Towns of Italy Resolutions, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- United Italian-American Labor Council Reports, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Resolution on Imports of Apparel, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Resolutions from Affiliated Groups, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Statements on Economic Policy, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Statement on Adlai E. Stevenson, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Resolution on Industrial Runaways and Plant Piracy, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Resolution on the State of Israel, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Resolution on Manpower Training, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- National Resources and Conservation and Anti-Pollution Measures, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 36)
- Resolution on Our Cities, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Radical Right, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Montreal Joint Board Resolution, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Foreign Policy- Search for Peace Resolution, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 40)
- Gloversville Agreements, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 41)
- General Executive Report and Supporting Documents, 1965-1969 (Box 16, Folder 42)
- Resolutions on Organizing, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Union Label Resolutions, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Education Program Resolutions, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Insurance Program Resolutions, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Pension Program Resolutions, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Resolutions from Affiliates, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Report of the General Executive Board, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  [Empty]
- Amalgamated Health Centers, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Medical Services, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Banks, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Retiree Services, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Recreational Services, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Housing, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Appeals and Grievances, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Committee on Industrial Matters Reports, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Statement on Economic Policy, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Resolution on Manpower Training, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Area Redevelopment, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Resolution on Severance Pay, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- War on Poverty Resolution, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Wage and Hour Legislation, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Walsh-Healey Public Contracts Act, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Unemployment Insurance Resolution, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Workmen's Compensation Resolution, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Resolution on The Nation's Health, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Resolution on Political Education, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Problems of Our Cities Resolution, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Housing Resolutions, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Nation's Public Schools Resolution, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- National Resources and Conservation Reports, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Women Workers Resolution, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- National Labor Relations Board, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Taft-Hartley and Landrum-Griffin Laws, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Resolution on Civil Rights, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- Civil Liberties, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Radical Right Resolution, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- Consumer Problems Resolution, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 37)
- 89th Congress, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 38)
- Social Security Resolution, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 39)
- Congressional Reform, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 40)
- Repeal of 14B Notes, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 41)
- Resolution from Affiliates, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 42)
- Foreign Policy- Search for Peace Resolution, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 43)
- Boys' Towns and Girls' Towns of Italy Resolutions, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 44)
- Israel Resolutions, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 45)
- ORT, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 46)
- United Italian-American Labor Council, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 47)
- Imports of Apparel Resolution, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 48)
- Canada Resolution, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 49)
- Resolution on Farm Workers, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 50)
- Law and Constitution, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 51)
- Committee Designations Convention, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 52)
- Convention Resolutions, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 53)
- Convention Departmental Reports, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 54)
- JT BD and Local Reports to GEB, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 55)
- New York World's Fair, 1964-1965 (Box 17, Folder 56)
- Letters to Resolutions Submitted by Affiliates, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 57)
- Resolutions on Organizing, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 58)
- Figure Head Resolutions, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 59)
- Union Label Resolutions, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 60)
- Amalgamated Banks Resolutions, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 61)
- Law and Constitution, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 62)
- War on Poverty Resolutions, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 63)
- Wage and Hour Legislation, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 64)
- Unemployment Compensation Resolutions, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 65)
- Medicare Resolutions, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 66)
- Political Education Resolutions, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 67)
- Immigration Resolutions, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 68)
- Regional Development and Conservation Resolutions, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 69)
- Labor Legislation, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 70)
- Civil Rights Resolutions, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 71)
- Civil Liberties Resolutions, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 72)
- Radical Right Resolutions, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 73)
- Day Care Projects, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Deansgate Notes, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Deborah Hospital Correspondence, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence. [Folder 1 of 6], 1968 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence. [Folder 2 of 6], 1968 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence. [Folder 3 of 6], 1968 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence. [Folder 4 of 6], 1968 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence. [Folder 5 of 6], 1968 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence. [Folder 6 of 6], 1968 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Herbert Ferster (Dreschler and Leff) Correspondence, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Henry Fleisher Correspondence, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Local Dues Increase Requests, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- GEB Meeting Agenda and Notes, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Local Dues Increase Approvals, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- General Executive Board Meeting Notes, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- General Executive Board Agendas, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Government Committee Scholastic Achievement Notes, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- February General Executive Board Meeting Notes, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Government Contracts, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Greater New York Fund, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- L. Grief and Company Correspondence, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Group Research Inc. Correspondence, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Hart, Schaffner and Marx Correspondence`, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Sidney Hillman Health Center Correspondence, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Hillman Foundation Correspondence, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Histadrut National Committee for Labor Israel Correspondence, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Chicago Hillman Health Center Correspondence, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Hubert Humphrey Correspondence, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Japanese-Hong Kong- Spain Imports Reports, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- International Leather Goods, Plastics and Novelty Workers Reports, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- International Industrial Organization and General Workers Union, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- International Garment Workers Federation Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Government of Israel Correspondence, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- International Ladies Garment Workers Union Correspondence, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Investment Reports, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence. [Folder 1 of 2], 1968 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence. [Folder 2 of 2], 1968 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Lyndon B. Johnson Correspondence, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Landrum-Griffin Correspondence, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Legal Department Correspondence, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- New York Teachers Correspondence, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Toward A Better America Book Correspondence, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Twin Pines Village Development, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- United Nations Correspondence, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence. [Folder 1 of 2], 1968 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence. [Folder 2 of 2], 1968 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- United Auto Workers Correspondence, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- United Jewish Appeal Convention, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Union Label and Service Trades Department Correspondence, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Urban Community Insurance Company Correspondence, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- US Government Agencies Correspondence, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- U.S. Department of Labor Trade Union Advisory Committee, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Textile Workers Union Correspondence, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Warbasse House Correspondence, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- United Housing Foundation Correspondence. [Folder 1 of 2], 1968 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- United Housing Foundation Correspondence. [Folder 2 of 2], 1968 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Urban Coalition Correspondence, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Warbasse Houses Reports, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- U.S. Senate and House of Representatives Correspondence, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence. [Folder 1 of 2], 1968 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence. [Folder 2 of 2], 1968 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- The Advance Mailing List, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Boss Manufacturing Company Agreements, 1973-1976 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- ANG Negotiations and Contracts, 1969-1971 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- EMKAY Form Letters (Box 21, Folder 4)
- BAW Manufacturing Company Correspondence, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Commercial Buildings Reports, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- CAR Insurance Company Form Letters (Box 21, Folder 7)
- ANG Negotiations and Contracts, 1969-1974 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Kincar Leasing Corporation Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- C.A.R. Leasing Contracts, 1969-1972 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Kinney Rent-a-Car Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Dixie Leasing, Inc. Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Connell Leasing, Inc. Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- T.V.I Leasing Information, 1967-1972 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Hertz Corporation Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Central States Insurance and Retirement Fund, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- EL Paso District Joint Board Reports, 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Collective Bargaining Agreements, 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- ACWA Comparative Statements, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- ACTWU Financial Statements, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- ACTWU Constitution, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Cotton Garment Agreements, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Ind. Fund Financial Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Drechsler and Leff- Robert Dales' Speech, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- ACWA Employment Possibilities, 1972-1975 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Fleming Joff Jentra LTD. Correspondence, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- GEB Dues Increase Reports, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- GEB Dues Increase Reports, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- General Economics Conditions Reports, 1974-1976 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Commissioner Carol Halter Correspondence, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Labor Council for Latin America Advancement Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- Levi-Strauss Company Correspondence, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 33)
- Levi Strauss Negotiations, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Levi Strauss EL Paso Labor Agreements, 1969-1974 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Levi Strauss Correspondence, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- EL Paso Joint Board Correspondence, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Ford Foundation Correspondence, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Hortex-Billy the Kid, 1966-1973 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Hortex Correspondence, 1966-1973 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Phillips Van Heusen Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Puerto Rico Contracts, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Puerto Rico Insurance, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- ACWA Research Department Reports, 1970-1974 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Puerto Rico Minimum Wage Negotiations, 1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Howard Samuel Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Single Pants Survey Reports, 1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- State Political Action Fund Reports, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- ACWA Staff Problems Reports, 1973-1975 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Southern Staff Reports, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Southern Staff Union Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Tampa FL Joint Board Publications, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Margie T. Tooze Correspondence, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Union Square Realty Corporation Correspondence, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Union Square Realty Corporation Oil Burners Reports, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- University Seminar In Labor, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Wage and Price Controls Reports, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Zwicker Knitting Mills Correspondence, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- ACWA Biennial Convention Reports, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Industrial Matters Reports, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- ACWA GEB Resolutions, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Biennial Convention Agendas, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Biennial Convention Opening Session Notes, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Michael Berkowitz Co. Correspondence, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Val Wertheimer Correspondence, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Magdalena Hernandez Correspondence, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous Publications, 1973-1976 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- La Voz Latina Publication, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Texas AFL-CIO Labor Bank, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Sidney Hillman Foundation Reprints, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Hodkins Glove Company Correspondence, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Washington Convention Planning Notes, 1972-1974 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- P.L. Manufacturing Company Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Robert Hall Clothes Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Langley Park Motel Correspondence, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- TOA Manufacturing Company Correspondence, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Review Committee #9 Appointments, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Puerto Rico Minimum Wage Committee Reports, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Balzano Glove Company Case Notes, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Retail Organizing Drive, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Arlans No-Raiding Case Notes, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Bargain Town Case Notes, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- M. Hoffman and Co. Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Illegal Aliens Resolution (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Individual FARAH Case Reports, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Overseas and ANASCO Sports Reports, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Perfect Shirt INC. Correspondence, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- A. Sagner Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Rawlings Corporation Correspondence, 197 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Sagner Inc. Correspondence, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Texas AFL-CIO Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Miscellaneous Reports, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- FARAH El Paso Leaflet ULP, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 38)
- Merger Reports to General Executive Board, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 39)
- FARAH Manufacturing Co. Correspondence, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 40)
- El Paso Trip Notes- July, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 41)
- El Paso Trip Notes- April, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 42)
- FARAH Convention Notes, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 43)
- EL Paso Trip Notes July, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 44)
- El Paso Trip Notes May, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 45)
- FARAH Correspondence, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence. [Folder 1 of 5], 1971 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence. [Folder 2 of 5], 1971 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence. [Folder 3 of 5], 1971 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence. [Folder 4 of 5], 1971 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence. [Folder 5 of 5], 1971 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- J. Potofsky Minimum Wage Reports, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- National Conference of Christians and Jews Notes, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- NAACP Correspondence, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- National Foundation Correspondence, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- National Park Foundation Correspondence, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- National Urban League Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- New York Committee American Cancer Society Correspondence, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- New York Government Departments Correspondence, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- R. Nixon Correspondence, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Mayor of New York Correspondence, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Men's Fashion Association Correspondence, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Mimeographed Materials, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- J. Potofsky Correspondence, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Office Memos, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Reidbord Bros. Correspondence, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Retail Clerks International Association Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Frank Rosenblum Correspondence, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- M. Stans Secretary of Commerce Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Fusing Agenda, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Merger Materials, 1969-1971 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Xerox Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Cuett Correspondence Puerto Rico, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Van Heusen Correspondence, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Lase Cutting Machine Reports, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Misc. Imports Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Wall Art Manufacturing Co. Correspondence, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Far East Imports Reports, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Ana Manufacturing Co. Correspondence, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Alisa Co. Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Industrial Matters, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Mailing Department Samples, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- International Reports and Correspondence, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Convention Agenda and Notes, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- ACWA Financial Statements, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Elliott 6016 Machine Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- ACWA Financial Statements, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- ACWA Comparative Statement of Stamps, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Citizens Housing and Planning Council of New York, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- ACWA Staff Retirement Plan, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- The Amalgamated Bank of New York Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- ACWA Financial Statements and Reports S.D. Leidesdorf, 1970-1972 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- All State Car Rental Correspondence, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Department Store and Retail Employee Pension Fund, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Legal Petition, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- M. Finley Apparel Industry Reports, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1972-1974 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Supplemental Agreements and Correspondence, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Political Education Committee Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- FARAH Juarez Correspondence, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Citizens' Housing and Planning Council Correspondence and Articles, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- FARAH Miscellaneous Correspondence and Records, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Financial Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 17)